# **Supanun** Ittharat

22 Ghim Moh Link, Singapore, 271022 | +65-8344-0983 / supanunittharat@gmail.com

## **SUMMARY**

Extensive experiences in Order Management & Account Analyst. Ability to formulate action plans for problem solving. Outstanding relationship building skills and driven to succeed. Proficient multi-tasker and time manager. Jovial, infectious personality and a natural leader.

#### **EDUCATION**

•	Master of Business Administration (MBA)	2014
	from University of Newcastle, Australia	
•	Bachelor of Business Administration (B.B.A.) in Global Business	2012
	from Khon Kaen University International College, Thailand	
•	Manukau Institute of Technology in Auckland, New Zealand	2009
	ESOL Program during the summer semester	

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCES

# Order Management & Account Receivables Analyst of Procter & Gamble Pte Ltd, Singapore

March 2014 - Present

- Improve order fulfillment process work closely with Market planner & Sales to provide products based on customer's demand. Participate with a team to establish the tools that customers can use to upload in their systems then they can see valid/ updated codes, available stocks and allocation limit in daily basis.
  - Resulting in: reduced product out of stock issue at customers end & enhanced service level
- ❖ Eliminate non-quality orders by conducting monthly tracking report, analyze root causes and represent to internal team (MDO logistics & Sales organization). Analyze customer characteristics and adjust order cycle to match with customers' needs.
  - Resulting in: reduced time of processing orders, timely deliveries, eliminated non-necessary costs.
- ❖ Market's Deduction Owner sustain deduction target via weekly drumbeat with financial team and established escalation process & standardized tracking to team.
  - **Resulting in:** improved market daily deduction & results achieved above target by 20%, faster aged deduction clearing from 30 days to 26 days in average
- ❖ Market's Overdue Owner: daily monitor & follow up with team to ensure customers make payment on time, identify root cause of late payment, provide timely action plan & escalation steps.
  - **Resulting in:** reduced DSO (day sales outstanding) for market & decrease orders on hold due to credit blocked / exceeded

#### Marketing Assistant (intern) of

June 2011 - Dec 2012

# C.P Intertrade Co.,Ltd, Bangkok, Thailand

Developed the overall strategy for several product launches – wrote and managed marketing plan, product positioning. Conducted focus groups and usability testing to gather customer feedback. Provided understanding market, competition and sales process

Resulting in: grew 18% of company's sales

#### **Customer Service of**

# Muang Thong Bhasaj Co., Ltd, Ubon Rathathani, Thailand

July 2009 - June 2010

Expanded medical business to Laos customers – conducted survey to understand customers' demand.
Responded on pricing inquiry, provide accurate and timely information. Established good relationship.
Resulting in: improved customers' satisfactions and they became loyalty customers

#### **SKILLS**

- Thai as native language
- Good command of spoken and written English
- Good understanding of Laos language
- Basic understanding of Mandarin
- Proficient in MS office applications, Adobe Photoshop, SAP, CRM, CMS supervisor, AVAYA and social media.